<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>assignment on</title><link>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/tags/assignment/</link><description>Recent content in assignment on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://jethughes.github.io/notes/tags/assignment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ass01-security-audit</title><link>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/ass01-security-audit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/ass01-security-audit/</guid><description>Security Audit for Awesome Web Site Jet Hughes - 9474308
Summary of system Function This system is a simple website for a store called Things &amp;amp; Co.</description></item><item><title>Assignment 02</title><link>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/assignment-02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/assignment-02/</guid><description>1 Introduction 1.1 Setup This report will discuss various strategies for managing a warehouse . A warehouse will be simulated as follows:</description></item><item><title>ethics-essay</title><link>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/ethics-essay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/ethics-essay/</guid><description>2000 words
6 paragaphs
350x4 + 300x2
Plan intro about the protests compare and contrast fire and fury with the river of filth about misinformation and censorship relate to videos compare misinformaiton and censoship in each of the videos critiques of fire and fury conclusion Intro 300 words</description></item><item><title>front-end-project</title><link>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/front-end-project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/front-end-project/</guid><description> spec
Links to sites:
https://jethughes.github.io/nzbirds/ https://cosc-203.cspages.otago.ac.nz/assignment-01/ Links to repos:
https://github.com/JetHughes/nzbirds https://altitude.otago.ac.nz/cosc-203/assignment-01 Features marks x Display: all photos by default 2 x Display: each bird’s name in both Māori and English 2 x Display: each bird’s conservation status in both text and colour 2 x Display: credit for each photo 1 x Form: search filtering 3 x Form: category filtering 3 x Form: Handle special characters (diacritics) 1 x Correctness: pass the W3C Validator 1 x Correctness: correct use of form and semantic elements 1 x Style: Responsive design 1 Style: looks nice 1 x Extra feature(s) bonus marks</description></item><item><title>hi-fi-development</title><link>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/hi-fi-development/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/hi-fi-development/</guid><description>Firstly I converted the lo-fi prototypes into Adobe XD designs.
I decided I wanted to make some chagnes to the design here so I saved this as version 1.</description></item><item><title>HW2</title><link>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/HW2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/HW2/</guid><description>Assignment 2 Jet Hughes 9474308
1. Let $V = P_2(\mathbb{R})$ with the ususal vector addition and scalar multiplication. For each of the following subsets of $V$, either prove that it is a basis of $V$ or explain why it is not a basis of $V$ .</description></item><item><title>Milestone 3</title><link>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/full-assignment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/full-assignment/</guid><description>Brain Storming Concept 1 - Snowboard trick generator. This will be a mobile app that snowboarders can use to automatically generate random tricks.</description></item><item><title>mobile-app-ass-03</title><link>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/mobile-app-ass-03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/mobile-app-ass-03/</guid><description> full-assignment
pdf
idea initial-ideas-mind-map brainstorming personas-development personas-final hi-fi-development
brainstorming brainstorming Personas and scenarios Development personas-development Primary Primary Casual Kyle Secondary Secondary Logan the learner Storyboard Low-fi Prototypes low-fidelity-prototypes drawings stage 1 drawing stage 2 more alternatives for navigation diagram more intial designs document add references to design heuristics Hi-fi Prototype Presentation</description></item><item><title>personas-development</title><link>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/personas-development/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/personas-development/</guid><description>Inital Ideas kyle the casual (primary maybe secondary) age 23 skill advanced focus: tricks aaron the coach (seconday maybe primary) age 30 skill used to be pro, now advanced focus teaching tricks logan the learner (seconday persona) age 16 skill intermediate focus not sure yet, beginning to experiement with tricks mac the professional (seconday persona) age 20 skill pro focus tricks, uses the app occaionaly with friends karen the parent (negative persona) age 45 skill intermediate focus, groomed runs, some backcountry phil the powder hound (supplementary persona) age 40 skill advanced (not with tricks just in general) focus off piste/backcountry, sometimes goes into park with friends/kids Final choices Primary: Kyle the casual Secondary: Logan the learner</description></item><item><title>personas-final</title><link>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/personas-final/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/personas-final/</guid><description>Primary: Casual Kyle Age: 23 Gender: Male Skill Level: Advanced (Not proffessional) Focus: Terrian Park Goals Experience goals wants a quick easy, no hassle, minimal effort experience.</description></item></channel></rss>