<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>assignment/mobile-app on</title><link>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/tags/assignment/mobile-app/</link><description>Recent content in assignment/mobile-app on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://jethughes.github.io/notes/tags/assignment/mobile-app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>hi-fi-development</title><link>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/hi-fi-development/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/hi-fi-development/</guid><description>Firstly I converted the lo-fi prototypes into Adobe XD designs.
I decided I wanted to make some chagnes to the design here so I saved this as version 1.</description></item><item><title>Milestone 3</title><link>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/full-assignment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/full-assignment/</guid><description>Brain Storming Concept 1 - Snowboard trick generator. This will be a mobile app that snowboarders can use to automatically generate random tricks.</description></item><item><title>mobile-app-ass-03</title><link>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/mobile-app-ass-03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/mobile-app-ass-03/</guid><description> full-assignment
pdf
idea initial-ideas-mind-map brainstorming personas-development personas-final hi-fi-development
brainstorming brainstorming Personas and scenarios Development personas-development Primary Primary Casual Kyle Secondary Secondary Logan the learner Storyboard Low-fi Prototypes low-fidelity-prototypes drawings stage 1 drawing stage 2 more alternatives for navigation diagram more intial designs document add references to design heuristics Hi-fi Prototype Presentation</description></item><item><title>personas-development</title><link>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/personas-development/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/personas-development/</guid><description>Inital Ideas kyle the casual (primary maybe secondary) age 23 skill advanced focus: tricks aaron the coach (seconday maybe primary) age 30 skill used to be pro, now advanced focus teaching tricks logan the learner (seconday persona) age 16 skill intermediate focus not sure yet, beginning to experiement with tricks mac the professional (seconday persona) age 20 skill pro focus tricks, uses the app occaionaly with friends karen the parent (negative persona) age 45 skill intermediate focus, groomed runs, some backcountry phil the powder hound (supplementary persona) age 40 skill advanced (not with tricks just in general) focus off piste/backcountry, sometimes goes into park with friends/kids Final choices Primary: Kyle the casual Secondary: Logan the learner</description></item><item><title>personas-final</title><link>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/personas-final/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jethughes.github.io/notes/notes/personas-final/</guid><description>Primary: Casual Kyle Age: 23 Gender: Male Skill Level: Advanced (Not proffessional) Focus: Terrian Park Goals Experience goals wants a quick easy, no hassle, minimal effort experience.</description></item></channel></rss>